Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
No living creature was harmed during the
filming of this series
We defeated the enemy, son.
They will attack us now.
For this reason, you will grow up.
You will grow so that the oppressed
may rest in our shadows.
You will get strong.
You have no other solution.
You're wasting your power in vain.
If you waste your strength like this, you
won't have the strength to defend.
Come on, get up.
You say my power ends
quickly, huh, Osman Bey?
It must be because of my weakness.
So, you will continue to defend
while you are on the ground.
Come up.
Son.
Give me your hand.
Come on, son.
Come on.
Your training is over.
Go and continue teaching.
Aladdin.
Come on, son.
Come on.
Come on, Aladdin.
Bala.
My Bey.
This pressure is enough for my son.
Practice with someone of your level.
Are you of my level?
The level becomes clear during the fight, Osman Bey.
Okay, then.
Come on.
Your strength has not
changed, my dear Osman.
And your beauty hasn't changed.
It's still the same as in the past.
Like the first day.
My Bey.
It's Hasan, the messenger who
will go to Constantinople.
Thank yıu.
You...
will hand this over to the emperor.
This dagger is evidence of
what is written in the letter.
When you get to
Constantinople, tell Konur.
Those who attacked us on the way will
try to attack us again.
I'm going with two more horses...
and helpers.
Let the moon light my way...
I will go without rest, my Bey.
Thank you. Godspeed you.
- Boran.
- Sir.
Take extra measures.
Send different Alps.
The enemy is different.
Their moves will be different.
Your command, my Bey.
The enemy is different, but...
we are not the same either.
I deserve the throne...
and Rome deserves me.
Osman, that idiot prevented my access to the throne.
But he will pay the price.
He will!
He knew everything.
He put a spy in my city.
Now, I will have a spy
in Yenişehir too.
This smell...
This is the smell of death.
Who are you?
What do you want?
I have gifts for you.
I'm Frigg, the messenger of death.
You ignoble!
I'll make you pay for this!
I'm Marta.
I've come to Yenişehir as a cloth
merchant.
I am sure you will love me very much.
I ask you...
Is the price of the throne only a spy?
No, no!
Not like that!
I'll take everyone around him!
I'll take this Beys from him.
I will create a cliff between them...
and I will push Osman.
He thinks he has agreed with that
cowardly and foolish emperor.
I will tear up that agreement.
I'll tear it up!
Macri's website
Is it enough?
Not enough.
The throne would have promised power
to all the sons of Rome.
And I will take your sons, Osman.
First, Orhan...
The young one will die in my hands.
My Beys, we are going to
Sarıpınar for hunting.
That place is dangerous, Bey.
It's difficult for hunting.
A good hunter does everything.
This land is ours.
We will know every inch of it.
We'll know it so we don't become prey.
It's ours no matter what.
Let's go and hunt, my Bey.
My Bey, you are giving them a hard test.
What is your intention?
You know a Bey while hunting.
Let's put them to a hard one in distress,
so that we can rest on them in prosperity.
Come on, may our hunt be blessed.
Thank you.
Come on.
So, he goes hunting with his
Beys, doesn't he?
Yes, sir.
You are the prey, Orhan.
You interfered with the fate of this city.
And I will make you live in hell
in this world, Osman.
As for you...
Cardinal!
The Papacy will be very angry when
they learn that Osman killed you.
So, they will give me a very large army.
I will have the throne and kill
Osman at the same time.
So sad.
I'm sorry for everyone who tries
to stand against me.
- Well done, sisters.
- Thank you.
Mashallah, what did you cook, Ülgen Hatun?
Its scent reeks throughout the palace.
Fill me a plate.
No.
Sisters, make a roll of
bread for him.
I won't give food to anyone.
It's for Orhan Bey.
Thank you, Ülgen Hatun.
Thank you.
Oh, this smell...
Don't do that, Cerkutay.
No...
I can't stand it...
Cerkutay.
Ülgen Hatun.
Eat, Cerguday, eat!
Stop.
I will give you that too.
Here's a spoon for you.
You weren't mad at me, were you?
No, no, why am I even angry?
Can I eat this food?
Yes, eat it
Stop.
I'll give you bulgur (kind of rice) too.
Enjoy it.
Thank you, sisters!
- You're welcome.
- Good evening.
Eat, Cerguday, it is for you.
Cerguday knows very well
He knows what Orhan Bey likes. That's why
I let him eat.
If he likes the food, Orhan Bey
will like it too.
Ülgen!
Oh, I'm late!
Yes, Malhun Hatun?
Come on, Ülgen, we're leaving.
- Have you finished preparing the food?
- Yes, it will be ready soon, Malhun Hatun.
Okay, then.
Come on.
Hurry up sisters, we're late.
- Salam Alaikum.
- Alaikum Salam.
Dursun Fakı.
Send messengers to Samarkand, Tabriz
and all the Turkmen tribes.
Alps!
Draw your swords!
Look.
Which one of you has a sword
sharper than your pen?
The homeland is protected by swords,
but is run by wisdom.
We will have students of knowledge.
For this reason...
Summon the mudarris (teachers).
They are welcomed in our lands.
This is good news, my Bey.
When the light of conquest is seen, the
fire of science is flared up.
This will make Yenişehir a
center of science.
Mashallah.
We are always looking for the future...
but we stick to our roots.
We dream of Yenişehir and beyond.
But we will never forget
what is behind us.
For this reason...
We will now go to inspect Karacahisar.
Your command, my Bey.
Öktem Tent
Oh my Allah.
Oh...
My mother.
My beautiful mother.
Batur is more than a brother to me.
His breath is mine...
and his soul is my soul.
Sleep in peace, mother.
Rest in peace.
What's wrong with you, woman?
I fell asleep a bit.
And I dreamt of my mother.
May Allah bless her.
She was crying.
She told me "my daughter...
take care of your brother Batur" she said.
- Take it.
- Thank you.
My mother gave birth to a son.
However, both my mother and father
left before they could embrace their son.
And I saw Batur as my son.
But I couldn't have a son for you.
You gave me hope, woman, you
gave me a soul.
She gave me Alçiçek.
May Allah give both of you a long life.
Also, don't you know it, woman...
thanks to Batur, I didn't need a son.
Tell me.
What worries you?
I have seen demons with horns.
They were screaming like a black curse.
They were dragging my brother
into a deep hole.
Don't do this, Hatun.
This isn't Batur's firs time leaving.
Raise your head.
Is this worthy of you?
I'm not comfortable, my Bey.
You followed Osman's orders.
- You sent my brother.
- Don't say that, Hatun.
Is there a limit for a hero whose
love for conquest ignites in his heart?
The headquarters of Makri
is the gate of conquests.
The door of the soldier is a conquest.
And the key to that door...
is in the hearts of Batur
and our Alps, Hatun.
You have to understand that.
Also, I want Batur to grow up
next to Osman Bey.
So that he will be in the right place.
He would be good Bey, wouldn't he?
Of course!
I know, Hatun, Batur will do
this job properly.
Look...
When the time comes...
When the death comes for me...
May Allah give you a long life, my Bey!
Then...
Batur will sit on that chair.
Inshallah...
with Osman Bey...
He will be a soldier in the country that
will rule the whole world!
Don't worry.
Makri
What happened here?
Alps!
Be careful!
If we hadn't seen the smoke...
we wouldn't know there was a massacre.
Are these the measures you have taken?
We couldn't do our job!
We did not prevent
the killing of people.
Osman Bey was right.
Who are you?
I am Olof.
Turks' executioner!
Alps!
If we die, we are martyrs.
And if we live, we are Ghazis.
Allah is great! Allah is great!
Attack!
Little Orhan.
Think of yourself as a hunter.
Let's attack, sir.
Wait! Not yet.
He will fall into our hands
while it hunts its prey.
- Did you kill those next to the horses?
- They're all dead, sir.
Mashallah.
Now!
My Bey.
Alps!
Attack!
My Bey! We have to get you out of here.
I will not leave my Alps alone.
Allah is eternal!
I came to get you, little boy.
Whoever tries to hurt me is hurt first.
You ignoble!
My Bey.
I will kill you.
But slowly...
You won't get away with it.
I'll tear you apart.
You won't even have a grave.
Osman will beg me to find your remains.
Alps!
Take your places.
Look around
to find out who did this.
"We belong to Allah and to
Him we shall return."
This...
My Bey.
The martyrs are the Alps of Orhan Bey.
- Track them down.
- Your command, my Sir.
Orhan.
My Orhan.
Gölge.
- Ayaz.
- Yes, Bey.
Take the flag
You go to Karacahisar
and we will follow their tracks.
Your command, my Bey.
If my son is hurt, I swear that
I will burn this world!
My Bey.
This way.
- Osman.
- Don't worry.
Orhan Bey won't be under
the control of the infidels.
Come on.
We have to search the chests.
Open these chests
Open.
These chests will not be opened.
I can't let you into town
without checking all the boxes. (chests)
Alps!
What's going on?
They don't let us open the chests.
Open the chests.
Stop.
These boxes are gifts to Osman Bey.
It was specially brought by
my brother Leo.
Who are you?
How dare you ask for this?
I'm Osman Bey's wife.
Bala Hatun.
So, you're Leo's sister...
Tell me what's your name.
Forgive me for being so bold.
You look like an important woman
but I couldn't tell who you are.
My name is Marta.
Marta.
It doesn't matter.
The gifts are so beautiful, Marta.
Mr. Leo's shop is on this side.
Marta.
- My beautiful sister.
- My brother.
It seems you have met Bala Hatun.
Thank you for the gifts, Marta, but...
it seems like Mr. Leo didn't
tell you anything.
Osman Bey doesn't take gifts from
merchants and pays for them.
Okay then, Bala Hatun.
- Okay, then! Welcome.
- Thank you.
Bala.
Bala Hatun.
Osman Bey's dear love.
Now you know Marta.
You will meet Frigg when you die.
Carry him.
Do you think you will live anymore?
If I wanted to, I would cut
off your head now.
I will cut it already.
But death will not be so easy
for you.
Osman's son.
You're basically dead.
And I'm the demon that's going
to cut you to pieces.
His father has come.
Tell me.
It wuld be your turn after your son.
But I can start with you.
We got you, my Orhan.
Brother!
You will be fine, my lion.
Stand up.
Do you think that what you did
will be unpunished?
Go back to your village.
You killed innocents.
You stole the gold we collected.
We punished you.
Stand him up.
Orhan!
My son.
I got you, I got you, son.
I got you, Orhan, I got you.
My son.
Olof.
The Turks are coming.
I was waiting for them.
Let them come and...
see this massacre they caused.
Hang on, my Orhan.
My son.
When we bury our martyrs...
you will be buried.
Look at me.
Before you pay for what've you done...
even the soil is forbidden for you.
The soil is worthy of you helpless ones.
As for us, what is
worthy of us is Valhalla.
You tried to kill my son.
I protected him from my eyes
in a silk swaddling gown!
You will die in pain.
Death is at your door.
You will all die.
Whoever touches my son or touches us...
will pay for it dearly.
You touch my son Orhan, right?
I will kill you.
So,you broke my son's fingers.
I'll cut off your fingers.
You will never be able to
hold the sword again.
harm an innocent person.
My son, huh?
What is broken heals...
Well, what about cuts?
Scream.
In my lands, only the voices of
the oppressed are heard.
No one will hear...
your voice.
Scream if you want.
No one will hear you.
What happened here, Öktem Bey?
My Alps.
Batur.
Be careful.
Alps.
Are you here to take your revenge?
If you did this to my Alps...
I came to kill you.
Are you the one who gave these
corpses the order to raid the village?
What's the matter, you
ignoble dog?
Are you the one who
gave them the order?
Öktem Bey is clearly not aware of it.
Put down your swords and let's talk.
It's too late to talk.
This is the time for revenge, Bayındır
Bey.
So, there is nothing for us to do.
Our swords will speak.
Öktem Bey!
Stop.
You draw your sword before
you take the command...
it means you kill yourself first, don't.
My command is the tears of the
mothers of these martyrs, Turgut!
Will I have mercy on these?
How do I have mercy on these, Turgut Bey?
Alps!
Öktem Bey!
Where did you hear that we leave
without revenge?
That we have mercy on who did that?
Where did you hear that?
Be patient, Öktem Bey!
Let's understand
what happened first.
And when it's time for revenge,
I swear I'll be by your side.
Be patient.
Where have you been, Aktemur Bey
I've been looking for
you since morning.
Why are you looking for me?
Did you talk to her?
Yes, I did.
What does she say?
Wait, let me catch my breath.
My throat is dry.
Should I drink something?
Sherbet seller, give us sherbet.
Thank you.
Tell me now.
What did she say?
Is her heart empty?
That will not happen.
That girl is tough.
Forget about her.
I will find a better one for you.
Thank Allah.
Thank you, my Bey.
You say it won't happen, right?
Does she love someone?
Good news!
What will you buy me?
Whatever you want, Ülgen Hatun.
Come on, what did the girl say?
Her heart is empty.
However, she is a brave girl.
She wants a brave man like her.
And?
Shewill not find someone braver than you.
You're right.
So, Bengi Hatun?
They bring fabrics from
different countries.
Fabrics that never seen in these areas.
So beautiful, Marta.
We should prepare Alçiçek's
dowry with you.
Me and my cloths are at your command, Bengi Hatun.
Bala Hatun.
A raid took place near Karaağaç.
Turks entered Makri village.
Turks?
Tell Turgut Bey quickly.
Come on sisters.
What do they say, Alçiçek?
Batur, my brother.
Tell Öktem Bey.
How does this happen?
My uncle Batur Alp works
to protect Christians.
Peace is on.
Which Turkmen disobeys the order
of Osman Bey and attacks Makri?
Don't worry, there is clearly
something wrong with this.
Alps!
Let's go to the tribe quickly!
I don't know who you are
and what you are.
But if your hand is stained with
the blood of our Alps...
there is no escape for you.
Your men burned the village
and took the gold.
And I took their souls.
The price of blood is paid with blood.
If I wasn't here for peace...
I'd kill you.
I will kill you and your dogs!
You ignoble dog!
Stop, Öktem Bey!
Öktem Bey!
I know your pain, Öktem Bey.
I had many martyrs in my tribe.
I lost many martyrs.
Not now!
You will leave now and go...
but don't forget...
You will account for the massacre you
carried out and the gold you took.
Öktem Bey!
Turgut Bey!
Is this death appropriate?
We will not leave our Alps here.
It's a good thing I didn't kill you.
The dead you ask for...
Your bey Osman is the one who
will come and take them.
Stop.
Stop
Not now.
Olof.
The moment I put my hand down...
the breath you take will be the
last.
We are good at fighting...
and we also fight lies and slander.
But we always know that the truth
will come out sooner or later.
If I find out that you are behind this, I
will rip your liver out with my own hands.
But now, I'm here to make peace.
Don't worry.
Our leader is one.
Osman bey will come and take our martyrs.
Until then...
your breath is counted.
Know its worth.
Trust me Öktem Bey.
Go back to your tent.
Let's go, Alps!
Come on.
Constantinople, Emperor's Palace
In order to claim Byzantium throne...
one must have the blood of the
dynasty.
My commanders, my advisors...
The Crown Princes with
whom I am linked by blood.
I don't know where the enemy is.
Maybe in my nearest place.
If you only look at the places near you, you
will not be able to see the big picture, Emperor.
That is, I will change my point of view
if I can not change events.
Right?
If you let me, I'd like to question the
keeper Sarkis and all who were there.
Don't worry, Kantakuzenos.
My daughter Ophelia is in the ring now.
Ophelia.
Water the ring with your sweat, lest it is
watered with your blood.
Raise your shield.
Yes.
My Bey.
Have we been exposed?
Are you their leader?
I am Sarkis.
The arena keeper.
I am the most loyal servant of
your dynasty.
Then, you also fought for
my father on that bloody day.
Yes, Princess Ophelia.
The lives of us mortals are of no value to
the soul of a great emperor.
We fought against traitors.
An act so noble that we do not expect
from slaves
Well, aren't you in
charge of this arena?
Yes, I am.
Where were you when those
traitors slipped into the arena?
Where were you when they
came through the doors?
Where were you when the
Emperor's life was being targeted?
Princess Ophelia, we...-
Your moves were spoiled
when the Turks came.
You changed your side, too.
No slave would give up on hi life
for the sake of a noble.
Catch him.
As Princess Ophelia would like...
Great Emperor
A unit of Osman Bey attacked the town of
Makri, near Marmaracık.
They killed the Christians.
This... is not possible.
We left our brothers to them!
We shouldn't have trusted
Osman from the beginning.
We have a peace agreement, he can't
be the one who did this.
The taxes were distributed in Makri.
So, gold has blinded Osman's eye.
This should not be left unaccounted for.
Gold, Kantakuzenos?
I gave him more than that.
Osman isn't the one to do this.
I will learn what happened
If you'll excuse me, I can
find out what's inside.
You will go as my representative.
You will learn what happened and tell me.
Immediately.
And I'll never come back
here before I learn.
Excuse me.
I have work to do here before then.
Karacahisar Castle
Hold your breath, son.
No...
but he will hold the reins
of his management.
Orhan, get on your feet.
You fell into the trap.
You fell into the hands of the enemy.
You make your mother bandage
your wounds too!
Orhan
who does not bandage his own wound...
can't heal.
You will do your own thing.
You will...
so that you will have strength.
Put your finger back in place now.
You made me the Bey of Karacahisar.
- Son.
- I don't want it, mother.
Leave it, mother.
I do what I can do
to be fit for my position.
Trust your son, Osman Bey.
I used to see you small and hold you to my
chest because you are my son...
You became a strong Bey.
I didn't notice that.
My goal is to be a
son worthy of Osman Bey.
Who is Osman Bey to accept you?
What is important is...
to be acceptable to Allah.
What is important...
is to be worthy of Allah.
Öktem Tent
I feel bored, Alçiçek.
No news yet. I can't stand here.
Öktem.
My Bey, welcome.
Where is Batur?
Is he outside?
Hatun...
Why aren't you telling us anything?
Hatun.
He must be hungry now. Is it easy to
raise the sword against the infidels?
Let me summon him.
Hatun.
Batur is not here.
He will not come.
No.
I see you only speak evil.
- Hatun.
- Don't tell me that!
Batur fell a martyr.
We couldn't take his body.
But we will take him.
We'll take him.
Where is my brother, Oktem Bey?
I will bring him.
You brought him neither alive nor dead!
Hatun, I'll bring him.
Couldn't you take him?
I'll bring him, Hatun!
Stay patient!
- Couldn't you take him?
- Hatun!
Couldn't you take him?
I will bring him!
Did you leave him to those ignoble dogs!?
Why do you carry this sword?
May I, my Bey?
Come in, Huseyin.
You can get out.
Yes, tell me, let's see, Huseyin.
Talk about what you saw and heard.
Suddenly infidels raided, my Bey.
They were disguised as alps.
They killed the people
in the village first.
And then the Alps of Oktem Bey.
Who did this?
Did you see them?
Olof, his name is Olof, my Bey.
Olof ha?
Olof.
Don't tell anyone until we understand
their purpose in this attack.
Keep tracking those dogs.
I'll track them, my Bey.
Are we not going to tell
anyone about this?
Stop there, Huseyin.
Let Osman Bey weaken.
Let him weaken so that we gain
power more easily.
We will say what we know
when the right time comes.
But not now.
Macri Area
Osman did not reach his goal, my love.
The messengers he sent to the emperor
exist no longer.
They must have thought how beautiful
the angel of death is...
...while you kill them.
I don't think
they could think of anything.
Osman will experience the pain of
losing a child.
I'll take Orhan from him.
He'll pay for every drop of Saga's blood.
He will sent this as an evidence
to the emperor.
It's Saga's.
Saga.
Osman!
He came just as we were about to
kill Orhan.
We lost all our men.
Dan, Dan, where is he?!
He was captured by Osman.
So he was captured by Osman!
Frig!
Go to Yenişehir right now and wait
for my word.
We will hurt Osman.
Tell me what's going on in Karacahisar.
I had provisions counted.
Our warehouses are full.
Merchants come from all over the world
Our market is growing, my Bey.
I also detected the poor.
The aid will reach them soon.
I always do the job I've seen
from my elders, my Bey.
Let's eat then.
In the name of Allah
the merciful, the compassionate
Enjoy your meal.
Ask me the question that
stops you from eating.
Who are the ones who attacked me, Dad?
We came to this world for a test, son
We came to fight the devil
But most people do not know about this.
These demons are the ones who attacked you.
We don't know how they attack,
when they attack.
But this does not prevent us
from defeating them
Because there is no victory
for the devil against Allah's people.
Orhan!
Under this earth is full of these demons.
We are growing bigger.
The greater we are, the more enemy
we will have.
But we will trample them all, Inshallah.
Our problems get bigger,
but we get bigger as well.
We will fight, Inshallah, mother!
Mashallah! (praise be!)
You have the power to fight.
Yes we have.
We have.
Come on, Orhan.
Eat your food and comfort your father
when the time comes.
Come on.
Do you know why Osman went
to Constantinople?
Our worries are out of our heads,
Bayindir Bey!
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about who caused these
worries, Bengi Hatun.
They attacked the emperor.
Our Osman Bey went to save him.
He obviously stepped on someone's tail
while protecting him.
You want to say that these dogs
came to hurt us.
If they really didn't do
anything in that village
This means that our men died
for nothing.
There are no deads, Bayindir Bey.
There are martyrs.
Eyvallah. (Right)
Thank you.
Mother...
You haven't eaten anything.
At least drink this.
I won't take a bite until
my brother's body arrives.
We shouldn't have left the valiants there.
If it wasn't for Turgut Bey...
They are just trying to stop us.
If it was not for Osman...
...We wouldn't be broken.
If it wasn't for Turgut...
We wouldn't leave our martyrs there.
Does that Turgut call himself a Bey
after he left our martyrs to infidels?
I want my brother, Oktem Bey.
You will find me in my brother's
empty grave until he comes
Tomorrow morning
I will bring our martyrs and avenge us.
The axe of whom set up the trap that day.
The signs are the same.
You say the ones who attacked us and
the ones who attacked Orhan are the same.
We see them whenever
we are in a trap.
This means that they are the ones who attacked
the village and killed the innocents.
Batur and his followers followed this too
and wanted to stop them when they saw it.
But they killed our martyrs.
These snakes blamed them
after they killed them!
They started after
we protected the emperor
Apparently, they are trying to
drag us into the war.
They want to drag us into the war
In order to weaken us and the emperor.
There is someone they hide in the dark secretly
in these attacks, Osman Bey.
They are waiting for me to
deliver the martyrs.
Now that they have a game...
Let's say game on.
We will be careful.
When I face them...
You will take martyrs.
We will not forget the martyrs of course,
and the treachery surrounding them
We have to hurry now.
Oktem may do something crazy
before we arrive.
The fire of revenge ignites his heart.
Their intention is clear.
We are on a thin rope.
If it breaks...
Then we will find ourselves
broken on the battlefield
But we will not allow this.
We'll find the person behind them first.
Oktem.
He will stay behind
the curtain of secrecy
We'll raise that curtain
and dig their roots!
It's tme to start things now.
This is my brother Boran.
And I am Cerkutay.
I am not a sword, gentlemen.
You can't make me good
by beating me!
I am the great wave
that will bring you down!
But all these wounds are open
he will smell!
Masha Allah (praise be)
We'll salt you now
so you don't smell like that
Open, open, open, open!
You idiots!
Do you think you can scare a man who
defeated seas to come here with salt?
I will whip your head
and cover it with camel skin
Stop, stop, stop!
I will talk.
Constantinople.
You opened the gates for them.
Come on, confess!
Confess that we kill you quickly!
We and the Turks saved the emperor.
Turk's are gone.
We are here.
And you, princess, would like to kill
us who prevented the attack.
You're the one who wanted
to kill the emperor, right?
Are you accusing me of
trying to kill my father?
So it was you who would sit on the throne
after the emperor died?
But you failed!
You will pay the price
for this disrespect!
Soldiers!
Princess Ophelia!
I always have a secret weapon and secrets.
But I am not going to
be disrespectful for you.
My body and soul is
under your command.
You are not the guilty.
You are clearly on my side.
But... stop
Stand up
But I am not a person
whou would kill her father.
I am always at your command,
Princess Ophelia.
Well, who was this?
What is happening here?
The interrogation continues,
Kantakuzenos.
We are looking for the traitors.
Well, what did he tell you?
He told that the emperor
was aimed to kill.
But he doesn't know who did this.
Did he also tell how he got those
traitors into the arena?
Did he tell what he did while Sen Tahor
deploy his men?
He didn't.
The ring was under his responsibility
The things that happened
is his fault.
Prince Kantakuzenos,
leave him now!
There is nothing else
we can learn from these.
But obviously there are
others that we need to question!
This business is filthy and bloody.
Don't you worry.
I will catch them all and punish them.
Go to the palace, please.
I'll be back for you again Sarkes.
Don't forget that.
Our arena is always open to
Kantakuzenos.
I don't see a
good expression on your face
You obviously came
with bad news, what happened?
Oh, Prince Kantakuzenos.
Orhan is alive.
And Dan is captivated by Osman.
The cloud of mist is rising.
I thought of all possibilities I
win in every possibility
I will set off tomorrow.
Let's reveal the unknown.
Have your eyes on Ophelia and Sarkes.
Oktem's Tribe
Alps!
Blood for blood!
To avenge the martyrs, come on!
The great lord of the karken tribe,
Oktem Bey. Go and see
But there is a saying "who starts up in
anger sits down with a loss"
- Huseyin!
- Yes my Bey.
Prepare your alps.
We can't leave Oktem Bey alone.
What's it, Oktem Bey?
Join us if you want to help us.
But if you're here to stop us,
don't try, Boran.
It is the order of Osman Bey.
No one will go out of their tribe.
No one will draw their weapon.
Boran!
Will you make me shed a brother's blood
instead of avenging the martyr's blood?
The order is clear.
No one with a sword will
go out of their tribe!
If you don't stop, we might have to draw
our swords and shed blood, Oktem Bey.
It's not my fault now.
Stop!
Oktem Bey!
Boran Alp!
My sheik.
You let discord
walk around you, Oktem Bey.
My Sheik, don't.
Open my way.
Evil seems to be present
in your way.
So let me abide by the words
of the Messenger of Allah, who said:
"The sitting is better
than the one standing...
and the one standing is better than
the one walking when there is discord"
Sit down, Oktem Bey.
Sit down.
My sheik is right!
- Welcome my sheik!
- Eyvallah (thank you)
Falling out with each other
is what the enemy wants!
Calm down.
If Osman Bey told not to leave the tribe,
he must know something.
Yeni Sehir.
My condolences, Alcicek Hatun.
May Allah grant you patience.
Patience hah? Patience!?
My uncle went there by order
of Osman Bey
You are the reason
for what we lived!
How do you keep telling me to
stay patient?
Who are these, Subasi?
We got news this morning.
Osman Bey caught them when they
were about to attack Orhan Bey.
They raided the village first.
And they trapped Orhan.
It is clear that
they are attacking from all fronts
So you're telling me these are the ones
who killed my brother?
Ignobles!
Stop this Alcicek!
I will not let my uncle down!
Stop!
Bengi Hatun!
Get out of my way, Bala Hatun!
They killed our alps!
They took my brother from me!
Calm down!
Get away.
Alps!
Put your swords down!
Give me that dog!
The blood of alps
is on their hands!
Kill them!
They didn't even give us our martyrs!
How do you let this happen?
Let's say what we are doing is wrong.
Is what you are doing right?
How can you draw your sword
to a captive?
These dogs tried to kill my son.
While I allow them to survive
in order to find out the truth...
...what are you trying to achieve here,
Bengi Hatun?
You should have killed them there!
You shall not show mercy to the cruels!
We don't have mercy on anyone!
We bury our pain in our
hearts for the truth
Be a little patient, Bengi Hatun!
We all strive for the truth.
How long will I be patient, Bala Hatun?
My brother's grave is empty!!
We have an unfinished business now.
Alps!
Bring the horses, come on!
To the dungeon!
Alcicek.
Kill that dog at any cost.
Do it somehow.
Move! Move!
Hurry!
I won't leave you in their hands, Dan.
Marta, I brought you fresh fish.
It's time to move, Leo.
That Aladdin.
Let's find out...
...where he is.
I bear witness
that there is no god but Allah...
And I bear witness that Muhammad
is his Messenger.
The strength we got...
...has become famous all over the three
continents for years!
Who came from the cold northern waters...
...and turned The Mediterranean
into a lake of blood?
We, sons of north!
Who carries the cold north wind
and the fresh south breeze?
We, sons of north!
Vikings were our ancestors.
We have been giving our blood for Rome
for a thousand years.
We sacrificed our lives!
What did we get in return?
Their religion.
We worshipped their Gods!
While Rome was rotting
with fancy outfits and sweet smells...
We turned the Mediterranean
into a bloodshed!
But Rome couldn't take our souls!
Right now...
...It's time to take back what we have
been giving for a thousand years
We blew the wind of north
in Jerusalem.
Sometimes in Libya.
From gibraltarian to Nile Sea.
We carried the black curse!
For the blood of
every warrior we sent to Valhalla!
The north wind will blow
in Osman's land!
Now...
For my brother Saga!
Now!
For the sake of our warriors we have been
sending to Valhalla for a thousand years!
It's time to become the black curse!
May Allah be with you
Eyvallah my Bey!
You know what you'll do.
Bey, someone is approaching!
That's Kutan.
Cerkutay Alp is coming, my Bey.
My Bey!
They gouged the eyes of the three alps
that Oktem Bey had sent to watch.
Then they killed them.
They have been working with all their
power to shed blood, my Bey.
Traps and ambushes!
And the treachery even Satan
wouldn't think of!
All of these are
waiting for us.
So, we won't keep them waiting long.
The pits they dug will become their grave.
They are using our martyrs as a bait...
...they're waiting for us like a crow, Bey.
Turgut.
Show them that Turks won't leave their
martyrs without prayers.
There is a lot to suffer for that dog
before he dies, Osman Bey.
They wanted to remove
the emperor from his throne.
We prevented it.
We turned Constantinople upside down.
We ran to the fire with gunpowder.
And now they're messing with us.
Axes on their heads...
Who are these, my Bey?
What is their problem?
Those bastards wasted
their years for the nobles.
They must be careful, Cerkutay.
It is true what Turgut says.
There is a group inside
the palace that thinks...
the Emperor is weak
and helpless against us.
They are trying to seize
the reins of power...
and prevent us from advancing to the west.
But who stirred them up?
They are not alone.
If they risk everything to the point of
asking for the support of the Vatican...
I will never be surprised.
That's it!
They set up many traps to drag the emperor
into a war with us, my Bey.
They won't stop, Cerkutay.
They will create a lot of sedition to spoil the
peace agreement between us and the Emperor.
They must take advantage
of any opportunity
to finish their unfinished
business with the Emperor.
We have to prepare for a big war...
that this land has never seen before.
As if they weren't satisfied with killing
our Alps...
They also
shamelessly bullied Orhan Bey.
Now they are setting their
traps and waiting for us.
The blood of our martyrs has
not yet dried on their hands.
We will cut off their heads as much as
they broke my son's fingers.
This calling is from eternity and
will continue forever.
This call is Allah's call.
This call is a call to
eliminate the oppressors.
Allah is the greatest!
I will clean this black spot
on our forehead.
I'm going to make this
dog talk, you'll see.
and who are you?
I'll beyour death, dog.
What are you doing
here, Alçiçek?
Get away from me!
Let me make this dog speak
for my father's safety!
The truth can not be reached
by a wrong path!
What you're doing is punishing you.
Get. out of here before someone sees you.
Let her come.
Shut up!
Come and beat me.
You are said to be a strong woman.
I do not leave my
work unfinished.
I told you to get away from me.
I told you I'd make this dog talk.
Come on, let's talk, get over this guy.
Come on, what are you waiting for?
I told you to shut up!
I won't let you do this, Alçiçek.
Don't you understand
me, commander?
I told you to get away from me.
Don't make me hurt you.
You're basically hurting me
by doing this, Alçiçek.
This is not the time for stubbornness.
Get out of here before someone sees you.
- I told you I'd make him talk.
- Alçiçek.
Aktemur.
These pits will be filled
with their corpses.
They will all shed
blood for the blood of my dear Saga.
What if Osman doesn't come?
He will come.
They do not leave those of them.
If he doesn't come, we'll go to them.
I don't want any problem.
We will surround them when
they fall into the trap.
I have brought death to this country.
Like my grandfathers did in the
countries they conquered.
After Constantinople becomes ours...
I will conquer the whole world.
Ignobles.
Dig ,dig.
You are digging your own grave.
Constantinople
You're wondering why I let you
go, right?
No, princess.
I'm the only one you can
trust in the city.
You were there that day, who
do you suspect?
I doubt everyone, including you, princess.
Don't try to fool me
with any answer, Sarkis.
Where is Prince Kantakuzenos?
I'm so glad we were all thinking the same.
If you let me know where he is, I
can do more for you.
What's the biggest thing
you can do, Sarkis?
He is a member of the royal family.
I am so much more than
what you see, Princess.
And you should be happy
because I serve you.
This is touching.
Kantakuzenos.
He went to our lands
in the East by order of my father.
Him not being here is
safer for the throne.
He will attack those who stopped
the attempted coup.
Turks.
What are you thinking about that deep,
Aladdin?
Master Dursun.
I am very curious.
I am weak and had
to be a learner.
But you look so strong...
Why are you occupied with
science instead of fighting?
Aladdin.
Tell me, Aladdin.
Martyrdom is a pretty high rank, isn't it?
Of course.
And I want to be a martyr.
Now...
If I told you that our master the Messenger said,
"The ink of the scholars and
the blood of the martyrs...
...will be weighed
on the Day of Resurrection...
...and the ink of the scholars will
outweigh the blood of the martyrs."
What do you think of this, Aladdin?
I certainly believe what the Messenger
of Allah says, Master Dursun.
But I don't understand.
How is it possible? The ink of the scholars
is higher than the blood of the martyrs?
This happens when science is for the sake of
Allah, and spreading His name, Alaeddin.
We are fighting for the sake of
enjoining good and forbidding evil.
And during the conquests, we tell the verses
of Allah and the Sunnah of His Messenger.
Can we explain it without knowing
it first, Aladdin?
We can't do that, Master.
Of course we can't.
We will learn in order to inform.
We must first learn.
You should know that...
The more scholars spend ink...
The less our martyrs lose blood.
The ink is a shield for the martyrs.
But what if I want
to be a sword and not a shield?
Dear Judge...
Hadrat Judge.
I complain about
the merchants of Yenişehir.
They try to harm me
by using religion.
Stop there, Hatun.
Is this how you enter this room?
Excuse me, please.
But...
They want to pay me after many months.
And when I wanted to increase the
amount I would take from them...
...They object to it.
They say it's "interest"
and that it's forbidden, right?
And if I don't accept...
They say they won't take anything from me.
They say go and trade
in the Christian markets.
You will give me the names of
those who say so.
In these lands, everyone can carry out
their business according to the rules...
...as long as Osman Bey accepts it.
Those who threaten you will be judged.
But the thing you want
from the merchants is interest.
And our messenger of Allah...
...cursed the one who pays interest and
takes it and bears witness to it
Islam permitted trading
and prohibited interest.
So in this case, they will pay for
the fabrics they took in cash.
Honest merchants may come to you
but they don't have instant money.
There must be
a solution that makes everyone happy.
You will show your profit
when you sell your goods
And if the capital of your merchandise
increases after several months...
You will take your
profits from the customer.
This is Caiz (acceptable by the religion).
My Master Dursun is telling the truth
But, but that is not the issue.
Of course, science is important.
My dad doesn't give me
assignments because he doesn't trust me.
I know I'm not like my brother.
You have fallen into my hands now, Aladdin
Come on.
Enter that street!
Your hell is waiting for you!
Thieves! Who are you?
That's a trap!
I'm here, my Bey!
My Bey, call for help!
Run my Bey!
Are you okay?
My Bey!
They are approaching.
Let them.
Hell is waiting for them.
What is happening?
Osman.
You kill our alps.
You don't give us our funerals.
That's true.
Because you are the one I speak to.
What's more, in order to take our martyrs,
you set a trap for us.
You don't want peace.
Your intention is to break us.
I don't trust my enemy.
This is only a precaution.
Alright then.
We ignore it.
Now we will take our martyrs.
Come and take them if you can, Osman!
We have already taken our martyrs.
Sogut.
Oh...
The secret has been exposed.
The way is seen.
Thins are going crazy in Yenisehir.
Crazy as hell.
- Where are you going?
- The road is exposed.
Yenişehir is calling us!
We are going to Yenişehir!
"We belong to Allah
and to Him we shall return"
Amen.
Your blood will not be in vain,
my brothers.
It is forbidden for us to breathe
until we avenge!
Let's act alps!
This food is tasteless,
it tastes like barley!
Where are you, Cerkutay?
Are you full or hungry?
Shall I, Aunt Ulgen, taste it?
Taste it my daughter.
But something happened to me.
There is no taste for this food,
my dear Fatima.
It's too salty, Aunt Ulgen!
What?
What salt are you talking about?
This is just tasteless.
What is happening to me?
I can no longer taste the food!
Of course, this is because of
the absence of Cerkutay!
Oh Cerkutay! There is no taste in
this mansion when you are absent
Ulgen!
Have you seen Aladdin?
I haven't seen him, Bala Hatun,
what's wrong?
Allah Allah!
Where is this boy?
He must have gone to Master Dursun.
He should have come back by now.
Bala!
Our martyrs are with us, for sure.
Osman Bey.
As if you didn't already
give me a reason for war
The last thing you will hear
will be the trumpets of doomsday!
We'll be resurrected on the Day of Resurrection
under the banner of the Messenger of Allah.
But it is you
who have to fear the doomsday.
Alps!
Bala Hatun.
What happened?
Who attacked you?
They kidnapped Alaeddin Bey.
What?
We couldn't save him.
Son!
Alps!
Take him to the healing room
right now, come on!
Sisters, close all the doors of
Yenişehir, no one will leave!
Come on!
Alps, find me a trace of my son!
I don't get involved in a war
that has already begun.
I start the war.
This is your last chance.
The court will be held.
The truth will be revealed.
Blood don't need blood in return.
Blood needs blood, Osman.
Blood needs blood!
Alright then.
Your court will be held on the battlefield.
I trust you with my gift.
Take a good care of him.
We will hand him over
to his owner, madam.
By order of Bala Hatun, close the doors!
Alaeddin!
Where are you, baby?
Where are you son?
Alaeddin!
Bala, we'll find your son.
Ayse!
We will find him, Bala.
Bala Hatun!
We found Alaeddin Bey's hat and
his book, they're bloody.
My Alaeddin!
I will kill you with your weapon.
My axe is like Thor's hammer.
No one who doesn't deserve can carry it.
It's time for your trial.
Come to me now.
Osman Bey!
Stop!
I am here in the name of the emperor.
You are fighting the wrong enemy.
...I don't know whom you work with,
but...
You won't leave here empty-handed.
Let me explain it to you
The risen sword shall not lower
without blood on it.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com